Good evening ladies and gentlemen and welcome to another harness video with
the gorgeous harnesses of Mani Mu again. I promised you in the last video that
I'm going to show them to you in other outfit combinations and some of you or
yeah a lot of you said they didn't expect a harness video from me and I was
like what why? So here we are combining jumpsuits and harnesses so I hope it's
going to be to your liking and I thought well let's not combine any jumpsuit with
these harnesses but it's going to be a latex video as well so latex catsuits
and leather harnesses I hope you're going to have fun by the way I'm already
wearing the first piece or part of one set here because I combined this Inziva
jumpsuit with my Fernando Bellin boots and thought well there could be a belt
missing here so I think that's cool. First outfit let's go all black because
this is such a badass combination black 0.4 millimeter catsuit with a front zip
obviously and this cool black harness set. I think this really is my favorite
harness that of the four
I love the shine of this and how it's kind of subtle but exciting
on the other hand yeah I think this has the chance to be my favorite outfit in
this video as well oh by the way for an all black outfit with a black catsuit I
of course need a black cat say hello to Luna oh you think I still got something
to eat now. She's muttering me again and it looks great together.
Yes I'm bribing her. That's how you do it with cats. While I'm feeding the cat you
can watch the next outfit. This is a clash of colors, wow. Yeah, I already like the pink
harness a lot and together with the black latex, it is so cool. It's like a hell of
a clubbing outfit for a fidget party or whatever. So shiny, but pink and with the blue hair.
I don't know, I feel really colorful at the moment although I'm wearing a black
head suit. Anyway I love this combination again.
I'm going to change into the next latex catsuit, different color than black and stay tuned.
For the blue harness I picked a metallic peacock catsuit. It's a 0.25mm neck entry so no zipper in the front or the back.
I'm kind of like an ocean all different blue colors from my hair to the harness to the catsuit.
I think this is a cool look altogether.
and the metallic peacock is one of my favorite latex colors.
And now on to the next harness, which is a black one,
and I'm going to combine the black one with the metallic peacock as well.
Okay, that was the last outfit.
If you want to know more details about these cool harnesses, check out my other Marimu
video.
I'll link it... is it here?
I think it's here. I'll link it here and down below. And I have a discount code for Marimur.
You will find it in the description text down below as well. So yeah, these make great gifts
or treat yourself with one of them. I can recommend them. They're really cool. I like
The combinations with latex a lot, I think.
It adds a completely different touch.
But I also like the original combinations with the mesh bodysuits,
which you can see again in the other video.
Okay, I hope you're having a nice day.
See you in the next video.
Bye.